You know what a lot of y'all problem is?
You think this internet is a place for you to watch influencers.
Entertainment.
The government gets it.
Netanyahu and them get it.
But not enough of you get it.
We are in a time where anyone who's speaking has the ability to influence liberation or oppression.
You are taking in messaging.
You are taking in advocacy.
Arbitrators.
And every time that you watch all of us on this internet and you tell yourself, oh, these are just folks making videos.
You are lying to yourself.
And you absolve yourself of the responsibility of what to do with those people's voices and their messages.
Arbitrators.
Thank you.